https://www.mulberrysilks-patriciawood.com/privacy/

This privacy policy sets out how Mulberry Silks uses and protects any information that you give Mulberry Silks when you use this website.Mulberry Silks is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.Mulberry Silks may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.What we collectWe may collect the following information:Name and payment details.Contact information including email address.Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests.Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.What we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:To process your order and obtain payment.Internal record keeping.We may use the information to improve our products and services.We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address that you have provided.From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interest.SecurityWe are committed to ensuring your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect on line.How we use CookiesA cookie is a small file which asks for permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or let you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can be tailored to your need, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our web site in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You to choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other web sites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note we do not have control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Data aggregation, analytics and profile creationWe may analyse your browsing behaviour to draw inferences and create profiles about your personal preferences and behaviour. We may then use such information for the purposes described below:Behavioural advertising and cross platform targetinga) Served by usWe may use your information (including profile data) to serve you with advertising, which is relevant to you, on our website and the website of third parties.b) Served by third parties on our websiteAdvertisers or other third parties using our website may also engage in behavioural advertising and use cookies and web beacons in the manner described above. We do not control these advertisers or other parties’ use of cookies or web beacons or what tile data)hey do with the information they collect.c) Served by third parties on third party websitesWe may provide your personal information (including profile data) to third parties who may then use it in combination with personal information that they have collected from you to serve you with relevant advertising on third party websites.Controlling your personal informationYou may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can tick to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us.We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us you wish this to happen.You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to us.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.Product CategoriesBooksChristmas PacksConnoisseurFabricsLarger Amounts of One ColourMini TopicsRibbonsSilk TopicsSpecial Gift BoxesSpecial PacksSearch Products
Search for:
Subscribe to My Newsletter
Please leave this field emptyEmail *By subscribing you agree to receive my promotional marketing materials and agree with my Privacy Policy. You may unsubscribe at any time.Check your inbox or spam folder now to confirm your subscription.
About Mulberry SilksWe sell a unique and exclusive range of hand-wound Pure Silk Twist for embroiderers in Medium or Fine thickness.Search for Products
Search for:
Search
Customer ServicesTerms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyDelivery & PostageAbout meContact meSubscribe to My Newsletter
Please leave this field emptyEmail *By subscribing you agree to receive my promotional marketing materials and agree with my Privacy Policy. You may unsubscribe at any time.Check your inbox or spam folder now to confirm your subscription.
© Mulberry Silks 2019 onwards. All rights served. E&OE.
×
ShopCategoriesBooksChristmas PacksConnoisseurFabricsMini TopicsRibbonsSilk TopicsSpecial Gift BoxesSpecial PacksLarger Amounts of One ColourColour MatchingEventsGift VouchersContactMy Account
×
What are you looking for?
Search for:
Search
